<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Rohan Badwe</title>
    <link>https://rbadwe.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Rohan Badwe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© {2021}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 20:24:44 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rbadwe.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Imagesteganography</title>
      <link>https://rbadwe.github.io/blog/hiding-another-image-inside-an-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 20:24:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rbadwe.github.io/blog/hiding-another-image-inside-an-image/</guid>
      <description>What is Steganography? &amp;ldquo;Steganography is an art of hiding information inside information i.e. embedding it in some other data. Steganography is the practice of concealing a file, message, image, or video within another file, message, image, or video. The main objective of Steganography is mainly concerned with the protection of contents of the hidden information. Images are ideal for information hiding because of the large amount of redundant space is created in the storing of images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes</title>
      <link>https://rbadwe.github.io/blog/kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 20:23:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rbadwe.github.io/blog/kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>Q. What is Kubernetes? Kubernetes is a portable, extensible, open-source platform for managing containerized workloads and services, that facilitates both declarative configuration and automation. It has a large, rapidly growing ecosystem. Kubernetes services, support, and tools are widely available. Kubernetes automates the deployment, scaling, maintenance, scheduling, and operation of multiple application containers across clusters of nodes. Kubernetes contains tools for orchestration, service discovery, and load balancing that can be used with Docker and Rocket containers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
